Indiana University Department of Radio and Television Chair's records, 1939-1963 C104
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative files, 1937-1962
  - Subject files, 1939-1963
    - ACPRA (American College Public Relations Association) (Box 4)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 4)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 4)
    - AFM (American Film Market), 1951 (Box 4)
    - AFRS (Association for Education by Radio), 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - AFT (American Federation of Teachers), 1951 (Box 4)
    - AMP (Applied Measurement Professionals), 1943-1953 (Box 4)
    - Academic tenure and freedom, 1943; 1950 (Box 4)
    - Administrative study, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
    - Administrators' conference, undated (Box 4)
    - Admissions, 1950-1954 (Box 4)
    - Adult education, 1950-1954 (Box 4)
    - Adventures in living, 1952 (Box 4)
    - Advertising course, 1944-1950 (Box 4)
    - Adviser materials, 1950; 1953 (Box 4)
    - AER (Association for Education by Radio-Television), 1951-1953 (Box 4)
    - AERT (Association for Education by Radio Television), 1955-1957 (Box 4)
    - Airlines material, undated (Box 4)
    - Alabama, University of, 1954 (Box 4)
    - Allen, Andrew, undated (Box 4)
    - Allerton House, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Allied Universities TV council, 1952-1954 (Box 4)
    - American Association for Adult Education, 1951 (Box 5)
    - American Chemical Society, 1950 (Box 5)
    - American Council on Education newsletter, 1958 (Box 5)
    - American Universities field staff visitations, 1956-1957 (Box 5)
    - American women in radio and television (Box 5)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 5)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Annual radio-TV banquet, 1956-1957 (Box 5)
    - Anti-defamation League, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
    - APBE (Association for Professional Broadcasting Education) formerly UAPRE (University Association for Professional Radio Education), 1955-1957 (Box 5)
    - Archives, national, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Armstrong, Major E.H., 1951 (Box 5)
    - Arts & Sciences (Box 5)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 5)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 5)
      - Faculty minutes, 1951-1952; undated (Box 5)
    - Art by radio, undated (Box 5)
    - ASCAP (American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers), 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Association for Professional Broadcasting Education (Box 5)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 5)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Association of the Junior Leagues of America, Inc., 1954 (Box 5)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Audio visual photographic, 1952-1953 (Box 5)
    - Audio visual recording, 1953-1954 (Box 5)
    - Auditions, 1944-1948 (Box 5)
    - Austrian information center, 1950-1951 (Box 5)
    - Author's Playhouse, 1944; 1949-1950 (Box 5)
    - BMI (Broadcast Music Inc), 1945-1950 (Box 5)
    - Basketball, WFIU, 1956 (Box 5)
    - Basketball applications, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Basketball between half shows (Box 5)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 5)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 5)
    - Basketball halftime shows, 1953-1958 (Box 5)
    - Basketball permits, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - B.B.C. used order blanks, 1956-1960 (Box 5)
    - Best of the 48, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Bids, station, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Bill of Rights program, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Binford, H.E., 1950 (Box 5)
    - Biographies of Indiana University men, undated (Box 5)
    - "Black Bread and Schule", undated (Box 5)
    - Blind students, arrangements, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Boners, 1949; undated (Box 5)
    - Books, 1947-1951 (Box 5)
    - Bookstore, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Boosey and Hawkes, 1942 (Box 5)
    - Bower, Carolyn S., 1957 (Box 5)
    - Bremen radio, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - British Broadcasting Company, 1951 (Box 5)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Broadcast material, 1957-1959 (Box 5)
    - Broadcasting Foundation of America, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Broadcasting Magazine, 1952; 1954 (Box 5)
    - Broadcasting Music Inc., 1958; undated (Box 5)
    - Broadcasting schedules (IU), 1949 (Box 5)
    - Broderick, Gertrude C., 1953 (Box 5)
    - Bryan, William Lowe, "A Better World or None" (speech), undated (Box 5)
    - Budget (Box 6)
      - 1945-1951 (Box 6)
      - 1952-1958 (Box 6)
    - Buildings and grounds (Box 6)
      - 1952-1954 (Box 6)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 6)
    - Bulletin board materials (old), 1948; 1951 (Box 6)
    - CAA (Civil Aeronautics Administration) regulations, 1943 (Box 6)
    - "Caliphone", 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Calumet center, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Campus coxial cable, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Cancer material, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Carlson, Roy W., undated (Box 6)
    - Careers and salaries, 1951; undated (Box 6)
    - Carmony, Donald F., 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Casting procedures, 1956-1957 (Box 6)
    - Catalogs, equipment, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Catalog of programs released by the educational television and radio center for 16mm use, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Cavalcade of the news, 1946 (Box 6)
    - CBC (Canadian Broadcasting Corporation), 1947-1950 (Box 6)
    - CBC scripts, undated (Box 6)
    - CBS (Columbia Broadcasting System), 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Chandler, Gloria- recordings, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Chanel 13, 1958-1959 (Box 6)
    - Chaperone rules, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Chester, Giraud, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - Chicago, University of- roundtable, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Chicago video service, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Children's programs, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Chronology- development of radio and broadcasting, 1946 (Box 6)
    - Clear channel problem, undated (Box 6)
    - Clearance procedures, undated (Box 6)
    - Closed circuit television (Box 6)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 6)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 6)
    - Coffin, P. Pristam, undated (Box 6)
    - College by air, 1947-1950 (Box 6)
    - College by radio, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - College courses in radio, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
    - Columbia broadcasting system, 1937-1938; 1944; 1946 (Box 6)
    - Columbus Institute, 1948-1951 (Box 6)
    - Comedians, radio, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Commercial stations for educational broadcasts, undated (Box 6)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), 1958-1959 (Box 6)
    - Committee on utilization of teaching resources, 1956 (Box 6)
    - Communications center, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
    - Communications muddle, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Communist investigation, 1946 (Box 6)
    - Comparative literature, 1947-1949 (Box 6)
    - Conferences, 1948-1949 (Box 7)
    - Congressmen, 1949 (Box 7)
    - Contracts, licenses and releases, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Copyright data and law, 1944-1950 (Box 7)
    - Corwin "Commandments from Cucmonga", 1947 (Box 7)
    - Cost estimates, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Course outlines, 1959-1960 (Box 7)
    - Coverage maps, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Credit courses, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Credit courses (television) (Box 7)
      - 1958 (Box 7)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 7)
    - Crosby, John, 1948 (Box 7)
    - Curriculum committee (Box 7)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 7)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 7)
    - Curriculum material (new), 1953 (Box 7)
    - Dale, Edgar, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Dean's, meeting, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Democracy, definitions of, undated (Box 7)
    - Description sheets, undated (Box 7)
    - Detzer, Carl, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Dues, application for payment, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Editorializing, 1949 (Box 7)
    - Education- AM and FM radio and television stations by state and city, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Education, office of, 1957-1958 (Box 7)
    - Educational stations in the U.S. (list), 1945-1950 (Box 7)
    - Educational television, 1953 (Box 7)
    - E.G.S. bulletins, 1956-1958 (Box 7)
    - Empire state FM network, undated (Box 7)
    - Enrollment, I.U., 1956 (Box 7)
    - ERP, 1947-1948 (Box 7)
    - Evansville- Southwestern Indiana Educational Television, undated (Box 7)
    - Expenses incurred for "Music in the Life of Man" television pilot show, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Extension courses, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
    - Facsimile, undated (Box 7)
    - Faculty Council (Box 7)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 7)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Minutes- Arts and Sciences, 1958-1959 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Newsletter, 1956-1957 (Box 7)
    - Famous Hoosiers, undated (Box 7)
    - Farm Programming, 1948 (Box 7)
    - F.C.C (Federal Communications Commission) (Box 7)
      - 1947-1950 (Box 7)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 7)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1942; 1944 (Box 7)
    - Fellows, Jack B., 1957 (Box 7)
    - Filing Systems, 1947 (Box 7)
    - First annual survey, undated (Box 7)
    - FM development association, 1959 (Box 7)
    - FM network, 1951 (Box 7)
    - FM station costs estimates, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - FM and television stations by frequencies, 1948-1950 (Box 7)
    - FM promotion materials, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - "Food Becomes You", 1957 (Box 7)
    - Foreign visitors, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Foundation funds, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Frankfurt Radio, 1948-1949 (Box 7)
    - FREC (Federal Radio Education Committee), 1950 (Box 7)
    - Free records, 1950-1951 (Box 7)
    - Freed- Eisemann, 1948-1949 (Box 7)
    - Foundation projects, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Fulbright act, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Fund for adult education, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
    - Gifts, 1950 (Box 7)
    - General Education Board annual report (Box 7)
      - 1952 (Box 7)
      - 1953 (Box 7)
    - Geography Broadcasts, 1947 (Box 8)
    - German, Dept. of, 1949 (Box 8)
    - German Exchange Broadcasts, 1949 (Box 8)
    - German Honorary, 1948-1950 (Box 8)
    - German Radio Scripts & Photographs, 1949 (Box 8)
    - German Stations (organization, schedules, etc.), 1947-1950; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Governor Wright, 1945 (Box 8)
    - Gilpin's study, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Grading policies, 1947-1951 (Box 8)
    - Graduate School council (Box 8)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 8)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 8)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 8)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 8)
    - Gucker, Dean –Arts and Sciences, 1957-1959 (Box 8)
    - Guest Radio Speakers (Box 8)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 8)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 8)
      - undated (Box 8)
    - Halls of Residence vouchers, 1950 (Box 8)
    - History of Radio at IU, 1948-1950 (Box 8)
    - Hooper, C.E. Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 8)
    - Hours of Instruction, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - "Human Adventure, The", 1943-1944 (Box 8)
    - Huth, Arno (Bibliography), 1949-1950 (Box 8)
    - I.C.A.O. (International Civil Aviation Organization) monthly bulletin, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - I.E.R. (Institute for Education by Radio), 1948-1951 (Box 8)
    - I.R.E. (Institute of Radio Engineers), 1945-1946 (Box 8)
    - Ideas, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Identification cards, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Indiana Business Survey, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Indiana conference of higher education, 1958-1959 (Box 8)
    - Indiana State Radio Surveys, 1939 (Box 8)
    - Indiana University Report of Physical and Human resources, 1942 (Box 8)
    - Indiana University writer's conference, undated (Box 8)
    - Indianapolis Public Schools programs, 1937-1945 (Box 8)
    - Institute for Democratic Education, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - Institute for Education by Radio and TV (Box 8)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 8)
      - 1957-1959 (Box 8)
      - undated (Box 8)
    - Interdivisional Broadcasting Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 8)
    - Interference, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - Interference problems, 1950 (Box 8)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 8)
    - International Goodwill Network, undated (Box 8)
    - Inventory, 1946-1950 (Box 8)
    - Inventory of construction and planning, 1953-1954 (Box 8)
    - Invoices, 1943-1944 (Box 8)
    - Irregularity report, 1953-1963 (Box 8)
    - IU announcements, 1957-1959 (Box 8)
    - IU bulletin, 1950 (Box 8)
    - IU Foundation, 1947-1953 (Box 8)
    - IU roundtable, 1950 (Box 8)
    - IURTS (Box 8)
      - H.J. Skornia (Box 8)
        - 1948 (Box 8)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 8)
      - Radio research study (Box 8)
        - #2, 1955 (Box 8)
        - #5, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Joint committee on educational television (Box 8)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 8)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 8)
    - Jordan College of Music, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Kentucky Broadcasters Association (Box 8)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 8)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 8)
    - Kine Network Schedules, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
    - Kine Participants, undated (Box 8)
    - Kine Transactions, Completed, 1957-1959 (Box 8)
    - Kinescope Charges (Box 9)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 9)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 9)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 9)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 9)
    - Kinescope Equipment, 1955-1956 (Box 9)
    - Kinescope Network Records, 1958/1960 (Box 9)
    - KUSC, 1949 (Box 9)
    - KYW Educational Projects, 1939-1963 (Box 9)
    - Language courses by radio, 1949 (Box 9)
    - Latin American radio, 1945 (Box 9)
    - League of women voters, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Legislative file, 1950; undated (Box 9)
    - Legislature, Indiana, 1951 (Box 9)
    - Lester script service, 1948-1950 (Box 9)
    - Letter to parents, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Letters, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
    - Lincoln Lore, 1944-1946 (Box 9)
    - Linguistics, 1950; 1952 (Box 9)
    - Listenables, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
    - Little 500, 1951 (Box 9)
    - Louisville Library, undated (Box 9)
    - Lowell Institute, 1948-1951 (Box 9)
    - Lyle, Harry M., 1958-1959 (Box 9)
    - Massey, Vera, 1947 (Box 9)
    - Materials and techniques of the women's director, 1956-1957 (Box 9)
    - McKinney, Robert, undated (Box 9)
    - Medical Center, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
    - Men's Faculty Club (Box 9)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 9)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 9)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 9)
    - Mittelhof, 1948 (Box 9)
    - MPPA, 1944-1945 (Box 9)
    - Muller, Prof. H.J., 1949 (Box 9)
    - Munich radio, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Music, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Music in Industry, 1943 (Box 9)
    - "Music in the Life of Man" programs, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Music, mood, 1948; 1950 (Box 9)
    - Mutual Broadcasting Systems, inc., 1946-1947 (Box 9)
    - NAB (National Association of Broadcasters) (Box 9)
      - General correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 9)
      - Harold Fellows visit, 1959 (Box 9)
    - NAEB (National Association of Educational Broadcasters) (Box 9)
      - Ford Foundation proposal, 1949 (Box 9)
      - Proposal for Grant-in-aids, 1952-1954 (Box 9)
      - Research- Grant-in-aids, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Tape network, 1955-1956 (Box 9)
      - Newsletter, 1956-1957 (Box 9)
      - 1954 (Box 9)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 9)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 9)
      - Newsletter, 1958-1959 (Box 9)
      - 1959 (Box 9)
    - NARTB (National Association of Radio and Television Broadcasters) (Box 9)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 9)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 9)
    - NWDR, undated (Box 9)
    - National committee for free Europe, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Leslie, 1949-1952 (Box 10)
    - Network program costs, 1949 (Box 10)
    - Nielson, 1945 (Box 10)
    - Non-academic appointments, 1954-1955 (Box 10)
    - Norvelle, Lee, 1947-1953 (Box 10)
    - Novik, M.J., 1950s (Box 10)
    - Oboler, Arch, undated (Box 10)
    - Ohio State Survey, open letter, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Open Letter, 1947 (Box 10)
    - Other materials from the advertising committee, 1949-1951 (Box 10)
    - Our geological heritage, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Out of state networks, 1949-1950 (Box 10)
    - PAC, 1948 (Box 10)
    - Peabody awards, 1942; 1948 (Box 10)
    - Policy statement IURTS, undated (Box 10)
    - Printing plant, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Prix Italia, 1955-1956 (Box 10)
    - Problems in human relations, 1949 (Box 10)
    - Production, 1958-1959 (Box 10)
    - Program analysis, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Program committee, 1952-1954 (Box 10)
    - Program Expansion, 1950-1951 (Box 10)
    - Program ideas, 1948-1950 (Box 10)
    - PGM (Playground Music) opens & closes, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Program openings and closings, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Program schedule (other statistics), 1959-1960 (Box 10)
    - Programming (Box 10)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 10)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 10)
    - Proposal for the reunion of instructors in Radio-TV, undated (Box 10)
    - PTA (Parent-Teacher Association), 1947-1948; 1950 (Box 10)
    - Publications (two folders), undated (Box 10)
    - Publicity, 1948-1953 (Box 10)
    - Purchasing department (Box 10)
      - 1951-1954 (Box 10)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 10)
    - Radio broadcasting- outline of radio programs (Box 10)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 10)
      - 1945-1946, (two folders) (Box 10)
    - Radio committee (Box 10)
      - 1950 (Box 10)
      - 1951 (Box 10)
    - Radio conference-reports of sessions, 1951 (Box 10)
    - Radio councils, 1948-1951 (Box 10)
    - Radio courses (Box 10)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 10)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 10)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 10)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - Radio curriculum (proposed), undated (Box 10)
    - Radio diffusion Francaise, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Radio guild, 1949-1951 (Box 11)
    - Radio Majors Accumulative Grade Averages, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
    - Radio Manufacturers Association, 1946-1947 (Box 11)
    - Radio panel discussion for "Stories to Remember", undated (Box 11)
    - Radio plans report, 1945-1950 (Box 11)
    - Radio Station, WLS, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Radio Station, WUOA, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Radio stations, how they may receive, 1950-1951 (Box 11)
    - Radio Survey, 1947-1948 (Box 11)
    - Radio-TV (Box 11)
      - Advising (Box 11)
        - 1957-1958 (Box 11)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 11)
      - Class Schedule, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
      - Committee assignments, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
      - Course enrollments, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
      - Course grades, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
      - Course outlines, 1958-1959 (Box 11)
      - Department (miscellaneous), 1957-1958 (Box 11)
      - Institute, 1952 (Box 11)
      - Summer internship program, 1957-1958 (Box 11)
    - Radio Writer's Guild, 1945 (Box 11)
    - Radio writing, 1947 (Box 11)
    - Raytheon ads, 1950 (Box 11)
    - RCA (Radio Corporation of America) (Box 11)
      - 1949-1955 (Box 11)
      - Educations IU news, 1959 (Box 11)
      - Victor records, 1950-1951 (Box 11)
      - Wave trap form letter, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Recording laboratory charges, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Record services, 1958-1959 (Box 11)
    - Red White Red, 1948-1950 (Box 11)
    - Regular weekly assignments, 1958 (Box 11)
    - Rek-O-Kut, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Reorganization of the Universities, undated (Box 11)
    - RIAS (Review of International American Studies) (two folders), 1949-1951 (Box 11)
    - Ricordi, G. & Company Inc., 1943 (Box 11)
    - Riley Memorial Association, 1949 (Box 11)
    - RMA (Riley Memorial Association) committee, 1949-1950 (Box 11)
    - Rochester School of the Air, 1946 (Box 11)
    - Rocky Mountain Radio Council, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Roundtable, 1949-1951 (Box 11)
    - Sabbatical leaves, 1947-1949 (Box 11)
    - Salary policies, 1948; 1951 (Box 11)
    - Sandler, Jerold, 1950-1953 (Box 11)
    - Schedules, program, 1949-1953 (Box 11)
    - Schinnerer, talk, undated (Box 11)
    - Scholarships (miscellaneous), 1956-1957 (Box 11)
    - Scholastic scripts, 1951 (Box 11)
    - School Broadcast Conference (Box 11)
      - 1947-1949 (Box 11)
      - 1950 (Box 11)
    - School of the Sky (Box 11)
      - 1947-1950 (Box 11)
      - 1950-1954 (Box 11)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 11)
    - School receivers, 1947-1948 (Box 11)
    - Schools of Radio, 1944; 1947-1948 (Box 11)
    - Schramm & Hudson, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Scott, Walter, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Scripts for Speed series, undated (Box 11)
    - Scripts, restricted, 1949-1950 (Box 11)
    - Scripts, sources, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Sebeok, Thomas, 1945 (Box 11)
    - Seminar in radio, undated (Box 12)
    - Service to crippled or blind students- examination, undated (Box 12)
    - Serving through science, undated (Box 12)
    - Sherwood, Dan, memorial scholarship, 1949 (Box 12)
    - "Shirts-Morris," thesis, 1952 (Box 12)
    - Siddons, George, 1947-1953 (Box 12)
    - Sigma Delta Chi award, 1950; 1953 (Box 12)
    - SITA (State Information Technology Agency), 1950 (Box 12)
    - Smyth survey, 1949 (Box 12)
    - Soap operas, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Socialism, 1950 (Box 12)
    - Sound effects (Box 12)
      - Catalogues, 1942-1952 (Box 12)
      - Turntables, 1945 (Box 12)
    - South Bend, Mishawaka Center, 1943 (Box 12)
    - Special projects courses, 1956 (Box 12)
    - Sport series, undated (Box 12)
    - Spot announcements, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
    - Staff meeting minutes, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Stage door, 1950 (Box 12)
    - State of the University, 1949 (Box 12)
    - State Fair, 1950 (Box 12)
    - Statement of policy, undated (Box 12)
    - Storesroom requisitions, 1953-1954 (Box 12)
    - Student loans, undated (Box 12)
    - Student staff, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
    - Studio theatre, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Stuttgart radio, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Subscription radio, 1945 (Box 12)
    - Summer session, 1957 (Box 12)
    - Summer listening, 1949 (Box 12)
    - Summer Talent (Box 12)
      - 1953, undated (Box 12)
      - undated (Box 12)
    - Summer workshop, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Superior student list, 1959 (Box 12)
    - Survey observations, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Syracuse University programs, 1942-1943 (Box 12)
    - Talent file, undated (Box 12)
    - Tape (Box 12)
      - Instructions to stations, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
      - Recording, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
      - Recordings SOTS (School of the Sky), 1950-1951 (Box 12)
      - Shipment inserts, undated (Box 12)
    - Tapes (Box 12)
      - Shipped and received, 1949-1951 (Box 12)
      - Sent, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Tarzian, 1946-1950 (Box 12)
    - Teacher's manual, 1953-1954 (Box 12)
    - Teacher rating sheets, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Television (Box 12)
      - Allocations, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
      - Course, 1947-1951 (Box 12)
      - Credit courses, 1956-1957 (Box 12)
      - Dealer-service questionnaire, 1950 (Box 12)
      - Cost estimates, undated (Box 12)
      - Frequencies for education, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
      - General, television, 1944-1953 (Box 12)
      - General, television, 1955-1956 (Box 12)
      - Interference, 1950; undated (Box 12)
      - News, 1948-1951 (Box 12)
      - Production reports, 1953 (Box 12)
      - Report, 1953 (Box 12)
    - Television programs, 1958-1959 (Box 12)
    - Television programs IU, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Television program logs (Box 12)
      - Programming, undated (Box 12)
      - Programs weekly (Box 12)
        - 1957-1958 (Box 12)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 12)
      - Aired, 1960 (Box 12)
      - Scripts, 1945-1950 (Box 12)
      - Set survey, undated (Box 13)
    - Television workshops, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Textbook (Box 13)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 13)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Theatre, undated (Box 13)
    - Themes, musical, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Thesis: "What Farm People Want from Radio," by Schmitz, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Tomasic, Dinko, 1945-1946 (Box 13)
    - Tower costs, 1947 (Box 13)
    - Tower lighting, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Town Hall Meeting of the Air, 1951 (Box 13)
    - Transcriptions available, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Transportation Indiana, 1950-1955 (Box 13)
    - Travel vouchers, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Tyo, John H., 1955-1958 (Box 13)
    - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization), 1947-1951 (Box 13)
    - Unidentified Film Reel, undated (Box 13)
    - United Nations Week, 1950 (Box 13)
    - University Bands, 1955 (Box 13)
    - University Broadcasting Association, 1958 (Box 13)
    - University Theatre, 1954 (Box 13)
    - University press, undated (Box 13)
    - Use of Televsion by Young School Children, 1955 (Box 13)
    - U.S. steel project, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Utilization of television films, 1955-1957 (Box 13)
    - Utley, Clifton M., 1951 (Box 13)
    - V.D. series, 1950 (Box 13)
    - Visiting critics, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Voice of America, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Vouchers, 1951-1954 (Box 13)
    - Western Lit (Mr. Kelly), undated (Box 13)
    - Wenner thesis, 1949-1954 (Box 13)
    - Willeford survey, 1947-1949 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Wendell L., 1953 (Box 13)
    - Wisconsin Idea, 1949-1951 (Box 13)
    - Women's programs, 1947-1950 (Box 13)
    - Word Study, 1944-1951 (Box 13)